Loudspeaker
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy
This world is flooded with color
Truth and lies dazzle our eyes
Look with your heart, look hard
You'll find the truth is not far away
Hey you good or bad, truth and lies
You can't escape this gray haze of the mind
Take all your courage with you
Maybe you can save this world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Uncle, Han Jiawei, and Inspector Sima ran into Taolesi
A fierce gunfight erupted between them
With their bullets spent, Uncle and Inspector Sima were in deadly peril
Han Jiawei stepped in and turned the tide
Jingjing was hiding under the shelves
Mr. K used Miss MU's autographed poster to lure her out of hiding
Then summoned a flower demon to chase Jingjing
Hawxing and Shaker each tried to persuade the other with their beliefs
But neither convinced the other
And so, the two are about to engage in a fight to the death
Hawxing transforms!
Hawxing, I must stop you!
Go!
Why did it go dark?
Oh no!
He slipped away.
Follow me.
He must be hiding up ahead.
I went through untold hardships
to finally regain the Magic Voice I'd lost.
Today I can finally put it to use.
Love and Dreams—
So beautiful!
So annoying!
How did I end up in this godforsaken place in the blink of an eye?
Where did everyone go?
Strange, I'm back where I started.
This kind of dumb thing really happens.
Hawxing, I advise you to stop resisting.
I really can spare your life.
Hawxing
Why are you always so stubborn?
You really won't find the feelings you're looking for here.
What I've decided to do
I will never give up easily.
Come on.
Shaker
Go!
You just won't see reason.
Love and Ideals—
What's wrong with us?
You guys, hurry up here.
Hawxing
Found the kid.
You be a good kid, okay?
Some sadness is inevitable.
Saying goodbye to today
Always leaves you feeling blue.
Look to tomorrow
Waving to me from the horizon.
Every day, the sun rises and sets
Spinning through time, dreaming more.
In life, I look forward to
Every second, every moment
Oh, bright eyes are sparkling.
A smile that greets the sunlight
Bravely speak the little feeling I've treasured in my heart
The morning breeze blows against my face
Carrying away wishes I've held for years
Breaking through the quiet at the Thousand Shores Station crossing
The Illumin-Eye
Today is your doomsday!